

+91 6392025617

mukulrajpoot262610@gmail.com

mukulrajpoot.com

LinkedIN in

GitHub 🔘

FIREBASE >

 SOLIDITY \$\square{\square}\$ GIT ♠

• C++ 🕲

JAVASCRIPT Js



 $\nabla$ 

# **EXPERIENCE**



2022 - PRESENT Software Developer Intern

2021 - 2021 Front-End Developer Intern

Mathrithms

### **ABOUT ME**

**SKILLS** 

• REACTJS ®

TAILWIND ≈

NEXTJS NEXT.

• REDUX &

NODEJS nede

MONGODB mongoDB

I'm a Front-End Developer based in Bareilly, India specializing in building exceptional digital experiences. I enjoy using my skill-set to empower people to accomplish their goals.

I create lighting fast WebApps and Websites using MERN Stack with the help of NextJS.

#### **PROJECTS**

2021 Full-Stack MERN Blogging Platform

Personal Project

It is a clone of dev.to website. I made this using MERN technologies.

00

2021 Worthpad DeFi

Freelance Project

I built their front-end part using nextjs and tailwind. And client was extremely happy about the work.

2021 Subira 2.0 - Document Signer

Internship Project

I built their front-end part using React, Redux and tailwind. I also did API integration using axios and redux async actions.

2022 **Ethereum Transfer Dapp** 

Personal Project

I built a ethereum transfer dapp, It can transfer ethereum without any middle person like bank. I used Next.js, tailwind, Solidity and Ethers.js to built this dapp.

00

**EDUCATION** 

2017-2019 **Emmanuel Mission School** 

Completed 12th standard

2020 - 2024 **Chandigarh University** 

Pursuing B.Tech CSE

## **COURSES**

NextJS: Build Full-stack **UDEMY** 

Apps, 2021

15+ hrs

Front End Developemnt, CODECADEMY

350+ hrs

MERN: The Complete **UDEMY** 

Guide, 2020

60+ hrs

React: The Complete LIDEMY

Course, 2019

40+ hrs

# POSITION OF RESPONSIBLITIES

HackOverflow Society Tech Team 2022-PRESENT

Member

2020-2021 Developer Student Club, Chandigarh